funformobile.com 2011-01-07

# FunForMobile: Privacy Policy

| Fun For Mobile |   
---|---|---  
  
### FunForMobile Privacy Policy

**Information Collection**

FunForMobile is the sole owner of the information collected on the Site. In order to use this Site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration, a user is required to give contact information (including name and email address) and other information. We also require a user's mobile telephone number in order to provide the services requested by the user. 

FunForMobile uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

Like most standard websites we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user's personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the Site for the user.   

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  

FunForMobile does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of FunForMobile's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
  * We transfer information about you if FunForMobile is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, FunForMobile will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

**Cookies**

  * FunForMobile may set and access FunForMobile cookies on your computer. 
  * FunForMobile lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to FunForMobile's cookies. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

We take security very seriously. We attempt to provide for the secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers by utilizing state of the art encryption software. However, due to the open communication nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and the Site, and the Site and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Users of the Site do so at their own risk. To prevent unauthorized access and maintain accuracy, the Site has in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to secure the information we collect on this Site. Employees with access to personally-identifiable information are required to follow our security rules, which state that such information must be used only for the purpose of providing services to you. These information access controls are regularly reviewed and updated.   

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

FunForMobile may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your FunForMobile account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Your Acceptance of this Policy**

By visiting the Site, you signify your assent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. 

**Contact Information**

We welcome any feedback and suggestion. For feedback, suggestions, support, and questions, please contact us using our Customer Support online form.  

Effective October 1, 2004  

Effective October 1, 2004
